<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<followup>
  <English>
	  <customer custname="TandF" custno="2556">
		  <from>sanches@datapage.org</from>
		  <to>software@datapage.org</to>
		  <cc></cc>
		  <bcc></bcc>
      <Sub>DTP Services</Sub>
		  <body>

        Hi Team,<br/><br/>

        This is Maria Sanches from <b>Datapage International Ltd</b> (<a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>) a leading provider of DTP solutions to top L10n companies. We operate from Coimbatore, India, and Dublin, Ireland.<br/><br/>

        We have around 320 highly skilled personnel and we provide a 24-hour-a-day, 3-shift process. The hallmark of our service is faster <b>TURNAROUND</b> times (<b>TATs</b>), quality service and competitive pricing.<br/><br/>

        We are specialised in the following domains:<br/><br/>

        1) Text extraction from any PDF format and in any language. We provide these services in 134 languages, including Chinese, Arabic and other right to left languages <b>(</b>see attachment<b>)</b>.<br/>
        2) DTP in all Adobe Creative Cloud and Suite Platforms, FrameMaker, QuarkXPress, etc. Also, we have proven expertise in CADD. Please refer to the attachment for a complete list of platforms we are familiar with.<br/><br/>

        The challenge in the <i>Localisation Industry</i> is competitive pricing and faster <b>TURNAROUND</b> times, and we at Datapage have consistently met client expectations in this regard. Our highly satisfied clientele would vouch for this fact.<br/><br/>
      
        I would welcome an opportunity to meet in person or talk with you to explore if innovative solutions offered by Datapage would be of benefit to <b>[COMPANY]</b>, and to this end, would be grateful if you could let me know a suitable time and day to meet or talk.<br/><br/>

  Kind regards,<br/><br/>
  <b>M. Sanches</b><br/>
  <b>Sales &amp; Customer Support</b><br/>
  <img src="cid:myImageID" height="25" width="85"></img><br/>      
  <font size="2">Datapage International Ltd., Docklands Innovation Park, 128-130 East Wall Road, Dublin 3.</font><br/>
  <font size="2">Mobile: +353 83 8180978, Landline: +353 1 4960628, Email: sanches@datapage.org, Web: <a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a></font><br/>

      </body>
	  </customer>
  </English>
  <Spanish>
    <customer custname="TandF" custno="2556">
      <from>sanches@datapage.org</from>
      <to>software@datapage.org</to>
      <cc></cc>
      <bcc></bcc>
      <Sub>Servicios de DTP</Sub>
      <body>

        Hola equipo,<br/><br/>

        Soy Maria Sanches de <b>Datapage International Ltd</b> (<a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>) un proveedor que lleva las soluciones de DTP para las principales compañías L10n. Operamos en Coimbatore, India y Dublín, Irlanda.<br/><br/>

        Tenemos alrededor de 320 empleados altamente cualificados y proporcionamos un proceso de 24 horas al día, en tres turnos. Una gran marca de nuestro servicio es el tiempo de respuesta más rápido (<b>TRR</b>), un servicio de calidad y precios competitivos.<br/><br/>

        Nos especializamos en las siguientes áreas:<br/><br/>

        1) la extracción de texto desde cualquier formato PDF y en cualquier idioma. Proporcionamos estos servicios en 134 idiomas, incluido el chino, árabe y otros idiomas de derecha a izquierda <b>(</b>véase el anexo<b>)</b>.<br/>
        2) DTP en todas las plataformas de Adobe Creative Cloud y suite, FrameMaker, QuarkXPress, etc. Por otra parte, hemos demostrado experiencia en CADD. Consulte el Apéndice para obtener una lista completa de las plataformas que conocemos.<br/><br/>

        El reto en el sector de la localización es en los precios competitivos y tiempos de respuesta más rápidos, y nosotros en Datapage hemos cumplido las expectativas de los clientes en este sentido. Nuestros clientes son altamente satisfechos y dan fe de este hecho.<br/><br/>

        Me gustaría tener la oportunidad de conocer usted en persona o solo hablar para ver si las soluciones innovadoras que ofrece Datapage serían beneficiosas para <b>[COMPANY]</b>, y también lo agradecería si pudiera decirme en un día y la hora adecuada para que nos encontremos o simplemente hablar.<br/><br/>

        Atentamente,<br/><br/>
        <b>M. Sánchez</b><br/>
        <b>Soporte al Cliente y Ventas</b><br/>
        <img src="cid:myImageID" height="25" width="85"></img><br/>
        <font size="2">Datapage International Ltd., Parque de Innovación Docklands, 128-130 East Wall Road, Dublín 3.</font><br/>
        <font size="2">
          Móvil: +353 83 8180978, Teléfono fijo: +353 1 4960628, Correo electrónico: sanches@datapage.org, Web: <a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>
        </font><br/>

      </body>
    </customer>
  </Spanish>
  <Portuguese>
    <customer custname="TandF" custno="2556">
      <from>sanches@datapage.org</from>
      <to>software@datapage.org</to>
      <cc></cc>
      <bcc></bcc>
      <Sub>Serviços de DTP</Sub>
      <body>

        Olá equipe,<br/><br/>

        Eu sou a Maria Sanches da <b>Datapage International Ltd</b> (<a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>) um fornecedor que lidera as soluções DTP para empresas de topo L10n. Operamos em Coimbatore, India e Dublin, Irlanda.<br/><br/>

        Temos cerca de 320 funcionários altamente qualificados e fornecemos um processo de 24 horas por dia, a 3 turnos. A grande marca do nosso serviço é o <b>TEMPO DE RESPOSTA</b> mais rápido (<b>TRR</b>), serviço de qualidade e preços competitivos.<br/><br/>

        Somos especializados nos seguintes domínios:<br/><br/>

        1) Extração de texto a partir de qualquer formato PDF e em qualquer idioma. Fornecemos estes serviços em 134 línguas, incluindo chinês, árabe e outros idiomas da direita para a esquerda <b>(</b>ver anexo<b>)</b>.<br/>
        2) DTP em todas as plataformas Adobe Creative Cloud e Suite, FrameMaker, QuarkXPress, etc. Além disso, temos experiência comprovada em CADD. Consulte o anexo para obter uma lista completa das plataformas que conhecemos.<br/><br/>

        O desafio na indústria de localização está nos preços competitivos e tempos de <b>RESPOSTA</b> mais rápidos, e nós na Datapage temos consistentemente atendido às expectativas do cliente a este respeito. Os nossos clientes estão altamente satisfeitos e atestam este facto.<br/><br/>

        Gostaria de ter a oportunidade de reunir-me pessoalmente ou conversar consigo para vermos se as soluções inovadoras oferecidas pela Datapage seriam benéficas para <b>[COMPANY]</b>, e ficaria igualmente grata se me pudesse informar um dia e hora adequados para nos encontrarmos ou simplesmente falarmos.<br/><br/>

        Atenciosamente,<br/><br/>
        <b>M. Sanches</b><br/>
        <b>Vendas e Suporte ao Cliente</b><br/>
        <img src="cid:myImageID" height="25" width="85"></img><br/>
        <font size="2">Datapage International Ltd., Parque de Inovação Docklands, 128-130 East Wall Road, Dublin 3.</font><br/>
        <font size="2">
          Celular: +353 83 8180978, telefone fixo: +353 1 4960628, Email: sanches@datapage.org, Web: <a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>
        </font><br/>

      </body>
    </customer>
  </Portuguese>
  <French>
    <customer custname="TandF" custno="2556">
      <from>sanches@datapage.org</from>
      <to>software@datapage.org</to>
      <cc></cc>
      <bcc></bcc>
      <Sub>Services de DTP</Sub>
      <body>

        Bonjour l'équipe,<br/><br/>

        Je suis Maria Sanchez de <b>Datapage International Ltd</b> (<a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>) fournisseur leader de solutions de DTP pour les meilleures entreprises L10n . Nous travaillons depuis Coimbatore, en Inde, et Dublin, en Irlande.<br/><br/>

        Nous avons près de 320 employés hautement qualifiés et nous travaillons 24 heures, avec 3 équipes. La caractéristique de notre service est avoir un <b>TEMPS DE RÉPONSE</b> plus rapide (<b>TRR</b>), un service de qualité et des prix compétitifs.<br/><br/>

        Nous sommes spécialisés dans les domaines suivants:<br/><br/>

        1) Extraction de texte à partir de n'importe quel format PDF et dans n'importe quelle langue. Nous fournissons ces services en 134 langues, y compris le chinois, l'arabe et d'autres langues de droite à gauche <b>(</b>voir pièce jointe<b>)</b>.<br/>
        2) DTP sur toutes les plates-formes Adobe Creative Cloud et Suite, FrameMaker, QuarkXPress, etc. De plus, nous avons une expertise reconnue en CADD. Veuillez consulter la pièce jointe pour obtenir la liste complète des plates-formes que nous connaissons.<br/><br/>

        Le défi dans <i>l'industrie de la localisation </i> est un tarif compétitif et des temps de réponse plus rapides et, c-hez Datapage, nous avons toujours répondu aux attentes des clients à cet égard. No clients son extrêmement satisfaits et ils l’attestent.<br/><br/>

        Je serais très heureuse de pouvoir vous rencontrer personnellement ou de discuter avec vous pour découvrir si les solutions innovatrices offertes par Datapage seraient bénéfiques pour, <b>[COMPANY]</b>, et vous serais extrêmement , reconnaissante si vous pouviez m’accorder un rendez-vous pour que nous puissions nous rencontrer ou parler.<br/><br/>

        Je vous prie d’agréer l’expression de nos sentiments les meilleurs,<br/><br/>
        <b>M. Sanches</b><br/>
        <b>Ventes Service Clients</b><br/>
        <img src="cid:myImageID" height="25" width="85"></img><br/>
        <font size="2">Datapage International Ltd., parc d 'innovation Docklands, 128-130 East Wall Road, Dublin 3.</font><br/>
        <font size="2">
          Mobile: +353 83 8180978, Téléphone fixe: +353 1 4960628, Email: sanches@datapage.org, Web: <a href="www.datapage.ie">www.datapage.ie</a>
        </font><br/>

      </body>
    </customer>
  </French>
</followup>
	

